RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 5. Legal Office, 1977-1994
  - Agency Files, 1994 (Box 6)
    - 1995-022
      - Psychiatric Security Review Board, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Public Safety, Dept. of, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Public Utilities Commission, Dept. of (Box 10)
        - Bio-Gen Report, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - Cable Television, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
        - CL&P Data for Rate Requests, Folder I, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - CL&P Data for Rate Requests, Folder II, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Consumer Council, Suit for Injunction, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - CT Natural Gas Corp., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - Federal Energy Regulatory Comm, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - Fletcher Electric Light Co., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - New Hampshire, Suit Against, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - SNET Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - SNET Rate Filings, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - Southern CT Gas, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
        - Telecommunications (1992-93) (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - United Illuminating Correspondence (1992-94) (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - United Illuminating Fuel Data (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Public Works, Dept. of, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Resources Recovery Authority, CT (CRRA), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Revenue Services, Dept. of (Box 12)
        - Folders I & II, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
        - Folder III, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Secretary of the State (Box 13)
        - Election, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Siting Council, CT, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Social Services, [Income Maintenance], Departments of (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Re Lorraine Manor, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Social Services, [Income Maintenance, Human Resources], Departments of, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Special Revenue, Dept. of (Box 13)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - Weekly Lottery Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - Transportation, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Treasurer, Office of, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1995-040
      - Attorney General (Box 60)
        - General, 1989-1994 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
        - Alim v. Connecticut, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - Check cashing suit, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - Claims, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - Downs case, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - Mashantucket Pequot Tribe v. Connecticut, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - Transportation, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Comptroller, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, Marvin Gate, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Interest on Lawyer's Trust Account Program (IOALTA), 1991-1994, undated (Box 60, Folder 11-15)
      - Public Health and Addiction Services, Dept. of, Reardon hearing, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Subject Files
    - 1995-022
      - ACP vs Pauline Kezar, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Finance Law, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Chapman, Mark F., Letter, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Chief State’s Attorney, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Conference on Municipalities, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Eastern States Exposition, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Electro Devices, Inc., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Environmental Systems Products, Inc. (ESP), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Fiscal Analysis, Office of (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Freedom of Information, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Gun Control, 1981-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Hartford, City of, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Hazardous Waste Management, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Health and Human Resources, Federal Dept. of, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Health Care Reform, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Indian Affairs Task Force, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Institute of Living, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Justice for Abused Children Task Force, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Justices of the Peace (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Kids Request About CT (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Legislative (Box 16)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - [Legislative] Management, Joint Commission on, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - Program Review Investigation Committee] (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - Regulation Review Committee, 1991,1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Long Term Health Care Study, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Management and Budget, Office of (Federal), 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - MDC, 1979, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Municipal Correspondence, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Municipal Government, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement and State Compliance, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Plainville Mall, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Private Activity Bond Commission, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Property Tax Reform Commission, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Protection and Advocacy for the Blind, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Quintilliano Letters, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Real Estate, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Reports, Misc., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Seawolf Homeporting, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Separation of Powers, circa 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
      - Sexual Harassment Training (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Shakespeare Theater/Stratford, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Teacher’s Retirement Board, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Tracy Thurman Letter, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Welfare Reform, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Winthrop Health Care Center, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Wiretapping/Electronic Surveillance, 1977-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Wood Pond, Gift of Land, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Yale Corp[oration] (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Special Elections
    - 1995-040
      - General, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - House of Representatives (Box 60)
        - 3rd District, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 18)
        - 8th District, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 19)
        - 26th District, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 20)
        - 43rd District, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 21)
        - 54th District, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 22)
        - 71st District, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 23)
        - 84th District, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 24)
        - 97th District, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 25)
        - 140th District, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Judge of Probate (Box 60)
        - Bridgeport, 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 27)
        - East Haddam, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 28)
        - Enfield, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 29)
        - Farmington, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 30)
        - Lyme, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 31)
        - Manchester, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 32)
        - Manchester, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 33)
        - North Haven, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 34)
        - Old Saybrook, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 35)
        - Thomaston, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 36)
        - Wallingford, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 37)
        - Washington, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 38)
        - Waterford and New London, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 39)
        - Westbrook, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - Senate (Box 60)
        - 7th District, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 41)
        - 10th District, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- Series 6. Subject Files, 1986-1994; 1995-040
  It is not clear from which part of the Governor's Office these subject files originated.
  - Affirmative Action plan for Office of the Governor, 1993-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Algonquin Gas Company, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Food Bank, 1989-1992, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Emergency regulations, 1991-1994 (Box 61, Folder 4-5)
  - Ethics Commission, 1988-1993, undated (Box 61, Folder 6-8)
  - Ethics Commission, Annual Statements, 1990-1992 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - General Assembly, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Residence Conservancy (Box 61)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Incorporation and by-laws, 1991-1993 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Tax and estate planning conference, 1991 April (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Grant applications and letters, 1991-1993 (Box 61, Folder 14-19)
  - High Sheriff, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Indian and casino gambling, 1986-1993 (Box 61, Folder 21-23)
  - Indian liaisons, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Lottery agent licensing, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Mashantucket Pequot compact, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Mohegan compact, 1993-1994, undated (Box 61, Folder 27-29)
  - Offers of reward, 1988-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Operation "Spring Flower", 1992 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Pawcatuck Eastern Pequots, 1992-1994, undated (Box 62, Folder 3-7)
  - Pawcatuck Eastern Pequots, HUD grant, 1990-1993, undated (Box 62, Folder 8-11)
  - Probate Court, 1991-1994 (Box 62, Folder 12-13)
  - Providence and Worcester Railroad's system design map, 1992 June-July (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Science center, 1993 September (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Senior citizen intern program, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 16-17)
  - Special session proclamations, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - US Air / British Airways, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Workers" Compensation Commission, 1990-1994 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Series 7. Photographs, circa 1990-1993; 2003-032
  - Photographs, circa 1990-1993 (Box 1-2)
    Photos taken by Tony Calabrese of the Dept. of Public Works. Mostly negatives.
    Unarranged.
- Restricted, 1995-040
  Originals of redacted records.
  - Records (Box 63)
  - Records (Box 64)
- Addenda, 1990-1992
  - 2009-012
    - Governor Lowell P. Weicker inaugural, Draft, 1990 December 6; 1 folder (Box 1)
      Draft of inaugural arrangements for January 9, 1991.
      This file is in Box 1 of Accession 2011-075
  - 2011-075
    - Governor Lowell P. Weicker inaugural, 1990 December 21; 2 copies (2 folders + 1 leather binder) (Box 1)
      Inaugural arrangements for January 9, 1991.
      Leather binder is in Box 2
    - State services shutdown contingency plan, 1991; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Review of the 1992-93 Connecticut budget, 1992 May 14; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Presentation to Fitch Investors Service, Inc., New York, N.Y.
    - Leather binder for inaugural arrangements (Box 2)
      On cover of leather binder: Connecticut state seal, "Lowell P. Weicker, Jr.", and "January 9, 1991"
</ead